<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/><updated>2017-04-04T14:28:54+02:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn//</id><title type="html">Tiger Knight - Empire War</title><entry><title type="html">Update 0.1.7.9</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/03/28/0179.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Update 0.1.7.9"/><published>2017-03-28T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-03-28T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/03/28/0179</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/03/28/0179.html">&lt;p&gt; Updated datatables to 0.1.7.9.&lt;br /&gt; Added datatables for shields and horses.&lt;br /&gt; I have noticed a increased number of chinese users to my site so I added the chinese locales of the items. &lt;!-- version history, changelogs --&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/games/TK/announcements/detail/469904564219306139&quot;&gt;Official patch notes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&quot;button&quot; data-toggle=&quot;collapse&quot; data-target=&quot;#officialpatch0179&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt;Expand official post&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div id=&quot;officialpatch0179&quot; class=&quot;collapse patchnotes&quot;&gt; &lt;h2 class=&quot;large_title&quot; href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/games/TK#announcements/detail/469904564219306139&quot;&gt;Update Announcement (0.1.79)&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;div class=&quot;announcement_byline&quot;&gt; 27 March - &lt;a href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198336925011&quot; class=&quot;whiteLink&quot; data-miniprofile=&quot;376659283&quot; target=&quot;_top&quot;&gt;Frittata&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class=&quot;announcement_body group_body_links&quot;&gt; &lt;div class=&quot;bodytext&quot; id=&quot;abody_469904564219306139&quot;&gt; Dear gamers,&lt;br /&gt;In order to update Tiger Knight to version 0.1.79, we will be bringing our servers down for maintenance on 28th March 2017. &lt;br /&gt;Servers will be unavailable for approximately 3 hours, with the exact times as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;Asia server：2017/3/28 15:00-18:00（GMT+08:00）&lt;br /&gt; NA server：2017/3/27 00:00 - 2017/3/28 03:00（PST）&lt;br /&gt; EU server：2017/3/28 07:00-10:00（GMT）&lt;/div&gt;If it fails to update normally please close Steam and relog in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Content of Update&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The first season of our new Ladder Tournament (trial version): ranked Command Mode and ranked Duel Mode. &lt;br /&gt;Rules of Ladder - Command Mode:&lt;br /&gt;1. Opening time: 19:00-21:00 each day.&lt;br /&gt;2. 5V5 Conquest Mode.&lt;br /&gt;3. Bronze, Silver and Gold ranks will enter the Intermediate Battlefield while Platinum and Diamond ranks fight on the Advanced Battlefield (units of corresponding levels are required). &lt;br /&gt;4. Battles produce general’s exp, adjutant’s exp, units’ exp, prestige and so on (excluding copper).&lt;br /&gt;5. The top 100 best players will appear on the ranking list of Ladder Tournament.&lt;br /&gt;6. Conquest Mode does not support the teaming up function for the moment.&lt;br /&gt;Rules of Ladder - Duel Mode:&lt;br /&gt;1. Opening time: 21:00-23:00 each day. &lt;br /&gt;2. Duel Mode will use General Assembly (see below).&lt;br /&gt;3. Battles produce general’s exp and exploit for those fighting, and a token for spectators to use when predicting the outcome. &lt;br /&gt;4. Players of all levels will enter the Intermediate Battlefield, and the properties of equipment will be at the highest Intermediate level.&lt;br /&gt;5. The top 100 best players will be on the ranking list of Ladder Tournament.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New game mode：Duel Mode - General Assembly&lt;br /&gt;Players will be fight 1 v 1, with the winner advancing to the next battle until they arrive at the final.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Map&lt;br /&gt;Arena (features in Ladder - Duel Mode - General Assembly)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/3/2913/33236160210_1b2574e9e7_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The arena is an important public facility in Roman society, and a place where the public gather to watch fights. In order to provide an exciting spectacle for the audience, the combat area is often broken into distinct scenes to simulate various parts of the Roman Empire's expansion. Combatants put their lives on the line each time they step inside the arena, fighting both for personal glory and to satisfy the bloodlust of the spectators. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Black Forest（Command Mode - Conquest）&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/4/3954/33236159530_1f26005e7a_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Germania was a region to the north of the Roman Empire. At that time Germany was vast and wild, and apart from some sporadic Germanic tribes, most of the region was covered by rolling forests. The dense vegetation and tall conifers blotted out the sky and covered the sun, creating a humid climate and a lingering mist – perfect for an ambush! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Telamon（Command Mode – Conquest）&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/3/2816/33236158770_a3197bbc3a_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Situated on the Apennine Peninsula, Telamon is a city originally founded by the Etruscans and later conquered by the Romans. During the Republic, this is where the Romans pushed back invading tribes from the north and finally defeated them. This campaign was decisive in conquering Cisalpine Gaul, further expanding Roman control northwards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Events&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Embrace Spring&lt;br /&gt;Players logging into the game from Mar 28th to Apr 28th will receive a Spring Gift Pack (which includes a 3-Day VIP card, 1000 prestige and 30000 copper).&lt;br /&gt;Time-limited tasks from Apr 1st to Apr 2nd.&lt;br /&gt;Fight in 8 Command Mode battles each day to win 1000 prestige.&lt;br /&gt;Participate in 3 Duel Mode battles daily to win 500 exploit.&lt;br /&gt;Join 3 PVE battles every day to win 10000 copper and a Supplies Pack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;150% Gains Event&lt;br /&gt;The timed 150% gains event opens at the following time (based on the server time):&lt;br /&gt;Mar 28th – Apr 4th 18：00-22：00 NA Server (PST)&lt;br /&gt;Mar 28th – Apr 4th 13：00-17：00 EU Server (GMT)&lt;br /&gt;Mar 28th – Apr 4th 19：00-23：00 Asia Server (GMT+08:00)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;First Recharge Event&lt;br /&gt;Mar 28th – Apr 25th, players charging any amount of money or buying any DLC will get a Ghost Axe and a 3-DAY VIP card. The gifts will be sent to the in-game box.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Timed Events for April Fool’s Day&lt;br /&gt;On Apr 1st, players attending this event can claim a limited fashion item - The Emperor's New Clothes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/4/3946/32776837154_5ce7e8654f_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adjustments&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Battlefield&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;After many rounds of discussion, the development team has decided to adjust the score calculation methods in Command Mode and PVE:&lt;br /&gt;1. In Command Mode, players will be encouraged to win through teamwork and those who prefer defensive roles will receive more reasonable gains. &lt;br /&gt;2. In Epic War, players will be encouraged to complete the mission quickly through teamwork rather than taking a longer time to achieve personal high scores.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Command Mode - Conquest: the battlefield will be divided into personal and team scores. The winners will receive both personal and team scores instead of the previous system, where only personal scores affect gains. Generally speaking, the overall gains of winners will be improved; exp and coppers will be more evenly distributed among team members. The defeated side will not be adjusted for the moment. However, both sides will see an increase in scores for rescues and occupying flags.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Command Mode - Siege: extra scores for winning the battle quickly and killing the marshal; and successfully guarding the gate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;PVE scores: the scores will be divided into personal score and team score, with the personal score being lowered. The team will get extra team score according to the time they take to break a gate. Less time means higher scores. The gains will be calculated according to both personal and team scores.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;PVE rate: personal score rate has been changed to team score rate judged by the time used to complete PVE.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The properties of enemies in PVE adjust according to the number of people on the battlefield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The time needed to recruit soldiers at the conscription site has been reduced from 1 second to 0.4 second. The restoration time used to conscript a soldier is decreased from 20 seconds to 10 seconds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The time-limited battle field – Squad Deathmatch is temporarily closed and will reopen after it is optimized. Time-limited 7V7 Command - Siege Mode will be open each day from 17：00 to 19：00 (based on the server time).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;General&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The turning speed of a general is improved. Different kinds of weapons and body weight will affect the general’s turning speed on the ground.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The speed of dagger weapons will increase 15% in combo moves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infantry equipment will have 20% more defense capacity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The speed buff provided to a general on horseback when commanding troops to use &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; “Following Action” and “Following Collision” has been removed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;When the player attacks through a teammate, the damage to the enemy will be decreased by 50%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soldiers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have increased the soldiers’exp to help boost units on the Intermediate and Advanced battlefield, and help the generals to train soldiers more easily and quickly.&lt;br /&gt;Basic units: soldier exp increased by 30%.&lt;br /&gt;Intermediate units: soldier exp increased by 20%&lt;br /&gt;Advanced units: soldier exp increased by 10%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The current infantry is weak when protecting the general, so their damage to the enemy’s general will be improved by 15%. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu - the duration time for infantry who use two-handed weapons will improve by 20% &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;when doing combo moves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu - the ranged defense capacity of Danyang Infantry is increased by 10%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu - the ranged defense capacity of Wu Fearless Squad is increased by 10%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu - the defense ability of Jiangdong Pikemen’s Pike-Shield Array skill is improved by 12%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu - the damage of Jiangdong Heavy Infantry’s Power charge strike skill is lowered by 20%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu - the HP of Wu Tiger Warriors is decreased by 10% and the damage of spear wall against infantry is lessened by 8%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wei - the damage of Zhongyuan Heavy Pikeman’s spear wall skill is increased by 15%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shu - the release speed of Xuzhou Heavy Infantry’s Javelin Volley skill is improved by 15%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Special Soldiers - the attack speed of Fearless Vanguard is increased by 20%. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The status icon of soldier’s BUFF is optimized and only shows the icon of the latest BUFF.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The performance of Charging throw skill is optimized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basic battlefield will be set to Play vs. AI by default.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;English content has been adjusted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the future, we will add an avatar customization function. For the moment, however, when players choose a certain force the corresponding fixed avatar will display.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bugs Fixed&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pressing “Z” would not show the whole detailed battle information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Incorrect movements of Rome’s Shield Wall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direction of attack was judged incorrectly in some cases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Task display was incorrect in PVE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Incorrect view of the player after execution has been fixed in most cases. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The direction of the general’s icon was wrong.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The movements of Rome’s throwing skills were incorrect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Incorrect display of the Hurl and Strike icon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“The soldiers’ skill does not satisfy demands” was wrongly displayed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The number inputted on the Search interface could not be emptied. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The wrong calculation of times a player uses a certain weapon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the pre-battle preparation, even after the player chose a new adjutant on the top right corner of the interface, the old adjutant would still be the one bounded to the units when entering the battle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;When player exited the battle abnormally the prompt showed incorrect information.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</content><summary type="html">Updated datatables to 0.1.7.9. Added datatables for shields and horses. I have noticed a increased number of chinese users to my site so I added the chinese locales of the items. Official patch notes Expand official post Update Announcement (0.1.79) 27 March - Frittata Dear gamers,In order to update Tiger Knight to version 0.1.79, we will be bringing our servers down for maintenance on 28th March 2017. Servers will be unavailable for approximately 3 hours, with the exact times as follows:Asia server：2017/3/28 15:00-18:00（GMT+08:00） NA server：2017/3/27 00:00 - 2017/3/28 03:00（PST） EU server：2017/3/28 07:00-10:00（GMT）If it fails to update normally please close Steam and relog in.Content of UpdateThe first season of our new Ladder Tournament (trial version): ranked Command Mode and ranked Duel Mode. Rules of Ladder - Command Mode:1. Opening time: 19:00-21:00 each day.2. 5V5 Conquest Mode.3. Bronze, Silver and Gold ranks will enter the Intermediate Battlefield while Platinum and Diamond ranks fight on the Advanced Battlefield (units of corresponding levels are required). 4. Battles produce general’s exp, adjutant’s exp, units’ exp, prestige and so on (excluding copper).5. The top 100 best players will appear on the ranking list of Ladder Tournament.6. Conquest Mode does not support the teaming up function for the moment.Rules of Ladder - Duel Mode:1. Opening time: 21:00-23:00 each day. 2. Duel Mode will use General Assembly (see below).3. Battles produce general’s exp and exploit for those fighting, and a token for spectators to use when predicting the outcome. 4. Players of all levels will enter the Intermediate Battlefield, and the properties of equipment will be at the highest Intermediate level.5. The top 100 best players will be on the ranking list of Ladder Tournament.New game mode：Duel Mode - General AssemblyPlayers will be fight 1 v 1, with the winner advancing to the next battle until they arrive at the final.New MapArena (features in Ladder - Duel Mode - General Assembly)The arena is an important public facility in Roman society, and a place where the public gather to watch fights. In order to provide an exciting spectacle for the audience, the combat area is often broken into distinct scenes to simulate various parts of the Roman Empire's expansion. Combatants put their lives on the line each time they step inside the arena, fighting both for personal glory and to satisfy the bloodlust of the spectators. Black Forest（Command Mode - Conquest）Germania was a region to the north of the Roman Empire. At that time Germany was vast and wild, and apart from some sporadic Germanic tribes, most of the region was covered by rolling forests. The dense vegetation and tall conifers blotted out the sky and covered the sun, creating a humid climate and a lingering mist – perfect for an ambush! Telamon（Command Mode – Conquest）Situated on the Apennine Peninsula, Telamon is a city originally founded by the Etruscans and later conquered by the Romans. During the Republic, this is where the Romans pushed back invading tribes from the north and finally defeated them. This campaign was decisive in conquering Cisalpine Gaul, further expanding Roman control northwards.EventsEmbrace SpringPlayers logging into the game from Mar 28th to Apr 28th will receive a Spring Gift Pack (which includes a 3-Day VIP card, 1000 prestige and 30000 copper).Time-limited tasks from Apr 1st to Apr 2nd.Fight in 8 Command Mode battles each day to win 1000 prestige.Participate in 3 Duel Mode battles daily to win 500 exploit.Join 3 PVE battles every day to win 10000 copper and a Supplies Pack.150% Gains EventThe timed 150% gains event opens at the following time (based on the server time):Mar 28th – Apr 4th 18：00-22：00 NA Server (PST)Mar 28th – Apr 4th 13：00-17：00 EU Server (GMT)Mar 28th – Apr 4th 19：00-23：00 Asia Server (GMT+08:00)First Recharge EventMar 28th – Apr 25th, players charging any amount of money or buying any DLC will get a Ghost Axe and a 3-DAY VIP card. The gifts will be sent to the in-game box.Timed Events for April Fool’s DayOn Apr 1st, players attending this event can claim a limited fashion item - The Emperor's New Clothes.AdjustmentsBattlefieldAfter many rounds of discussion, the development team has decided to adjust the score calculation methods in Command Mode and PVE:1. In Command Mode, players will be encouraged to win through teamwork and those who prefer defensive roles will receive more reasonable gains. 2. In Epic War, players will be encouraged to complete the mission quickly through teamwork rather than taking a longer time to achieve personal high scores.Command Mode - Conquest: the battlefield will be divided into personal and team scores. The winners will receive both personal and team scores instead of the previous system, where only personal scores affect gains. Generally speaking, the overall gains of winners will be improved; exp and coppers will be more evenly distributed among team members. The defeated side will not be adjusted for the moment. However, both sides will see an increase in scores for rescues and occupying flags.Command Mode - Siege: extra scores for winning the battle quickly and killing the marshal; and successfully guarding the gate.PVE scores: the scores will be divided into personal score and team score, with the personal score being lowered. The team will get extra team score according to the time they take to break a gate. Less time means higher scores. The gains will be calculated according to both personal and team scores.PVE rate: personal score rate has been changed to team score rate judged by the time used to complete PVE.The properties of enemies in PVE adjust according to the number of people on the battlefield.The time needed to recruit soldiers at the conscription site has been reduced from 1 second to 0.4 second. The restoration time used to conscript a soldier is decreased from 20 seconds to 10 seconds.The time-limited battle field – Squad Deathmatch is temporarily closed and will reopen after it is optimized. Time-limited 7V7 Command - Siege Mode will be open each day from 17：00 to 19：00 (based on the server time).GeneralThe turning speed of a general is improved. Different kinds of weapons and body weight will affect the general’s turning speed on the ground.The speed of dagger weapons will increase 15% in combo moves.Infantry equipment will have 20% more defense capacity.The speed buff provided to a general on horseback when commanding troops to use “Following Action” and “Following Collision” has been removed.When the player attacks through a teammate, the damage to the enemy will be decreased by 50%.SoldiersWe have increased the soldiers’exp to help boost units on the Intermediate and Advanced battlefield, and help the generals to train soldiers more easily and quickly.Basic units: soldier exp increased by 30%.Intermediate units: soldier exp increased by 20%Advanced units: soldier exp increased by 10%.The current infantry is weak when protecting the general, so their damage to the enemy’s general will be improved by 15%. Wu - the duration time for infantry who use two-handed weapons will improve by 20% when doing combo moves.Wu - the ranged defense capacity of Danyang Infantry is increased by 10%.Wu - the ranged defense capacity of Wu Fearless Squad is increased by 10%.Wu - the defense ability of Jiangdong Pikemen’s Pike-Shield Array skill is improved by 12%.Wu - the damage of Jiangdong Heavy Infantry’s Power charge strike skill is lowered by 20%.Wu - the HP of Wu Tiger Warriors is decreased by 10% and the damage of spear wall against infantry is lessened by 8%.Wei - the damage of Zhongyuan Heavy Pikeman’s spear wall skill is increased by 15%.Shu - the release speed of Xuzhou Heavy Infantry’s Javelin Volley skill is improved by 15%.Special Soldiers - the attack speed of Fearless Vanguard is increased by 20%. The status icon of soldier’s BUFF is optimized and only shows the icon of the latest BUFF.The performance of Charging throw skill is optimized.Basic battlefield will be set to Play vs. AI by default.English content has been adjusted.In the future, we will add an avatar customization function. For the moment, however, when players choose a certain force the corresponding fixed avatar will display.Bugs FixedPressing “Z” would not show the whole detailed battle information.Incorrect movements of Rome’s Shield Wall.Direction of attack was judged incorrectly in some cases.Task display was incorrect in PVE.Incorrect view of the player after execution has been fixed in most cases. The direction of the general’s icon was wrong.The movements of Rome’s throwing skills were incorrect.Incorrect display of the Hurl and Strike icon.“The soldiers’ skill does not satisfy demands” was wrongly displayed.The number inputted on the Search interface could not be emptied. The wrong calculation of times a player uses a certain weapon.In the pre-battle preparation, even after the player chose a new adjutant on the top right corner of the interface, the old adjutant would still be the one bounded to the units when entering the battle. When player exited the battle abnormally the prompt showed incorrect information.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Updated to 0.1.77.</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/03/14/0177.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Updated to 0.1.77."/><published>2017-03-14T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-03-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/03/14/0177</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/03/14/0177.html">&lt;p&gt; Thanks for the email notice about the update, I have now updated it to 0.1.77.&lt;br /&gt; You might notice that the datatables didn't have any major changes with the new patch. They added all the T9 and T10 items to the game that was already in the files. I'm currently working on changelogs, it will be a preview over what items have changed achieved through comparing the new patch-data with the previous patch-data. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/games/TK/announcements/detail/484539998444900083p&quot;&gt;Official patch notes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;button type=&quot;button&quot; data-toggle=&quot;collapse&quot; data-target=&quot;#officialpatch&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt;Expand official post&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!--Official post --&gt; &lt;div id=&quot;officialpatch&quot; class=&quot;collapse patchnotes&quot;&gt; &lt;h2 class=&quot;large_title&quot; href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/games/TK#announcements/detail/484539998444900083&quot;&gt;Update Announcement (0.1.77)&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;div class=&quot;announcement_byline&quot;&gt; 9 March - &lt;a href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198336925011&quot; class=&quot;whiteLink&quot; data-miniprofile=&quot;376659283&quot;&gt;Frittata&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; Dear gamers,&lt;br /&gt;In order to update Tiger Knight to version 0.1.77, we will be bringing our servers down for maintenance on 10th March 2017. &lt;br /&gt;Servers will be unavailable for approximately 3 hours, with the exact times as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;Asia server：2017/3/10 15:00-18:00（GMT+08:00）&lt;br /&gt; NA server：2017/3/09 23:00 - 2017/3/10 02:00（PST）&lt;br /&gt; EU server：2017/3/10 07:00-10:00（GMT）&lt;/div&gt;If it fails to update normally please close Steam and relog in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update Content&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Advanced Battlefield units (tiers 9 &amp;amp; 10) will be available from the Upgrade screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wei Leopard Knights&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wei Royal Elite Knights&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wei Central Guards&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wei Royal Cavalry Archers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shu Royal Vanguard&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shu Royal Strike Troop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;White Feather Warriors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shu Royal Crossbow Cavalry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hengjiang Shooters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Royal Archer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wu Royal Elite Infantry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jiefan Infantry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Late Empire Legionarius&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evocati Augusti&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New game mode for Time-limited Battlefield: Command Mode - 7V7 Siege is open. 7V7 Conquest Mode will be temporarily closed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can choose Time limited Battlefield during a set time each day,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opening Time: 18:00-20:00 (same server time-zones as those used for maintenance)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bugs Fixed&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;bb_ul&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Fire Arrow skill of the Jingzhou Crossbowman and the Shu Light Crossbowmen could cause horses to stagger incorrectly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Roman adjutant behaves incorrectly after using his shield.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;bb_h1&quot;&gt;For more fun please follow us at&lt;/div&gt;Steam community：&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/app/534500/discussions/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://steamcommunity.com/app/534500/discussions/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facebook：&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/tigerknight.en/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/tigerknight.en/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YouTube：&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCUUakGeTdTKiwPyBYQW3s7w&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCUUakGeTdTKiwPyBYQW3s7w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reddit：&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/TigerKnight/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/TigerKnight/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discord：&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;bb_link&quot; href=&quot;https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=https://discordapp.com/invite/zNUPQUh&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://discordapp.com/invite/zNUPQUh&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</content><summary type="html">Thanks for the email notice about the update, I have now updated it to 0.1.77. You might notice that the datatables didn't have any major changes with the new patch. They added all the T9 and T10 items to the game that was already in the files. I'm currently working on changelogs, it will be a preview over what items have changed achieved through comparing the new patch-data with the previous patch-data. Official patch notes Expand official post Update Announcement (0.1.77) 9 March - Frittata Dear gamers,In order to update Tiger Knight to version 0.1.77, we will be bringing our servers down for maintenance on 10th March 2017. Servers will be unavailable for approximately 3 hours, with the exact times as follows:Asia server：2017/3/10 15:00-18:00（GMT+08:00） NA server：2017/3/09 23:00 - 2017/3/10 02:00（PST） EU server：2017/3/10 07:00-10:00（GMT）If it fails to update normally please close Steam and relog in.Update Content New Advanced Battlefield units (tiers 9 &amp;amp; 10) will be available from the Upgrade screen.Wei Leopard KnightsWei Royal Elite KnightsWei Central GuardsWei Royal Cavalry ArchersShu Royal VanguardShu Royal Strike TroopWhite Feather WarriorsShu Royal Crossbow CavalryHengjiang ShootersRoyal ArcherWu Royal Elite InfantryJiefan InfantryLate Empire LegionariusEvocati AugustiNew game mode for Time-limited Battlefield: Command Mode - 7V7 Siege is open. 7V7 Conquest Mode will be temporarily closed.Players can choose Time limited Battlefield during a set time each day,Opening Time: 18:00-20:00 (same server time-zones as those used for maintenance) Bugs Fixed The Fire Arrow skill of the Jingzhou Crossbowman and the Shu Light Crossbowmen could cause horses to stagger incorrectly.Roman adjutant behaves incorrectly after using his shield.For more fun please follow us atSteam community：http://steamcommunity.com/app/534500/discussions/Facebook：https://www.facebook.com/tigerknight.en/YouTube：https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCUUakGeTdTKiwPyBYQW3s7wReddit：https://www.reddit.com/r/TigerKnight/Discord：https://discordapp.com/invite/zNUPQUh</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Updated to 0.1.76.</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/28/0176.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Updated to 0.1.76."/><published>2017-02-28T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/28/0176</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/28/0176.html">&lt;p&gt; Updated to 0.1.76. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; I added a comment sections, one general where you can drop a message with anything. Then the more interesting part would be that I gave each and every item it's own comment section, this is great for sharing ideas or keeping discussion around that particilar item.&lt;br /&gt; If you want to help me improve the site there is a small icon you can click to upload images, a good way to share a screenshot of the item. &lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Updated to 0.1.76. I added a comment sections, one general where you can drop a message with anything. Then the more interesting part would be that I gave each and every item it's own comment section, this is great for sharing ideas or keeping discussion around that particilar item. If you want to help me improve the site there is a small icon you can click to upload images, a good way to share a screenshot of the item.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SSL and minimizer</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/22/SSL.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SSL and minimizer"/><published>2017-02-22T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/22/SSL</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/22/SSL.html">&lt;p&gt; Just noticed my mailserver haven't been working since I fixed SSL, ~so if I havn't answer then I have probably have not recived your mail. It should be up and running now again.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Added rss in the footer.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Added the adjunts.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</content><summary type="html">Just noticed my mailserver haven't been working since I fixed SSL, ~so if I havn't answer then I have probably have not recived your mail. It should be up and running now again. Added rss in the footer. Added the adjunts.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Updated to 0.1.75.</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/21/0175.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Updated to 0.1.75."/><published>2017-02-21T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-21T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/21/0175</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/21/0175.html">&lt;p&gt; Updated to 0.1.75. As it was another patch so fast, I got the feeling I had to automize the process some more. Before I had to dump the files, run different scripts to clean up and parse the data correctly. Then change the patch number so it correctly generates the new data and like flip another number somewhere. Basically had a shitty process.&lt;br /&gt; Right now I'm really happy with the end result as I almost have to do no input myself. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; As you might have noticed I also added the data for all the &lt;a href=&quot;///cn/soldiers.html&quot;&gt;soldiers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Have a look at the roman ones! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/510002/&quot;&gt;Socii Hastati&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/510004/&quot;&gt;Iberian Auxilia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/510006/&quot;&gt;Imperial Legionaries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/510005/&quot;&gt;Legionaries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/510000/&quot;&gt;Leves&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/510003/&quot;&gt;Principes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; And a lot new weapons was added with rome(ofcourse). I'll list a few new ids here. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/18052006/&quot;&gt;Heavy Battle Trident&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/58040002/&quot;&gt;Greek Javelin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/58040003/&quot;&gt;Detachable PilumⅠ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/58040005/&quot;&gt;Detachable PilumⅡ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</content><summary type="html">Updated to 0.1.75. As it was another patch so fast, I got the feeling I had to automize the process some more. Before I had to dump the files, run different scripts to clean up and parse the data correctly. Then change the patch number so it correctly generates the new data and like flip another number somewhere. Basically had a shitty process. Right now I'm really happy with the end result as I almost have to do no input myself. As you might have noticed I also added the data for all the soldiers. Have a look at the roman ones! Socii Hastati Iberian Auxilia Imperial Legionaries Legionaries Leves Principes And a lot new weapons was added with rome(ofcourse). I'll list a few new ids here. Heavy Battle Trident Greek Javelin Detachable PilumⅠ Detachable PilumⅡ</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tiger Knight Roman Empire</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/19/rome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tiger Knight Roman Empire"/><published>2017-02-19T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-19T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/19/rome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/19/rome.html">&lt;p&gt; Updated to 0.1.73 (rome), looks like they tweaked almost everything everything. One new variable was added (nSwitchWeapon) and a few new items. I'll figure something out to represent patch changes later. &lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Updated to 0.1.73 (rome), looks like they tweaked almost everything everything. One new variable was added (nSwitchWeapon) and a few new items. I'll figure something out to represent patch changes later.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Huh, that’s pretty neat</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/17/huhneat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Huh, that's pretty neat"/><published>2017-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/17/huhneat</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/17/huhneat.html">&lt;p&gt; I hope you like the new bootstrap theme!&lt;br /&gt; I certainly really like one thing. Noticed while I was debugging the site on the phone, the &quot;server status&quot; panel turned out pretty nicely, made sure it shows on-top in the flow if you visit the site from a mobile device. Felt pretty good to just check the page on the phone to see if the servers was online/working again. ~neat. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; I think I'll have a look on the new patch data today or tomorrow, I'm pretty psyched for the patch both in the aspect of the game and the new data!&lt;br /&gt; So my plan right now is to: &lt;br /&gt;1. Get all the data &amp;gt; Update the datatables&lt;br /&gt;2. Compare the new data with the old &amp;gt; Add a item changelog page.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; We will see how it works out, I haven't yet made any for of script for automation on comparing the new data with the old and spit out a somekind of changelog files. Updating to the new data for Tiger knight should not be a problem and should work out without that much effort from my part. &lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">I hope you like the new bootstrap theme! I certainly really like one thing. Noticed while I was debugging the site on the phone, the &quot;server status&quot; panel turned out pretty nicely, made sure it shows on-top in the flow if you visit the site from a mobile device. Felt pretty good to just check the page on the phone to see if the servers was online/working again. ~neat. I think I'll have a look on the new patch data today or tomorrow, I'm pretty psyched for the patch both in the aspect of the game and the new data! So my plan right now is to: 1. Get all the data &amp;gt; Update the datatables2. Compare the new data with the old &amp;gt; Add a item changelog page. We will see how it works out, I haven't yet made any for of script for automation on comparing the new data with the old and spit out a somekind of changelog files. Updating to the new data for Tiger knight should not be a problem and should work out without that much effort from my part.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Going Bootstrap</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/14/bootstrap.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Going Bootstrap"/><published>2017-02-14T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/14/bootstrap</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/14/bootstrap.html">&lt;p&gt; Currently working on the new theme, takes some time as I'm switching to bootstrap and changing the full look of the site. I think that's the next thing I'm trying to finish. &lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; You can see online players and the server status on the frontpage now, just some extra useful website candy. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;More on the datatable keys&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt; The names in the datatable is a bit wierd and not always understandable, with time I'll make it more pretty. Right now it's just more or less a raw dump. &lt;p&gt; Attackspeed of a meleeweapon in the game is calculated by: &lt;blockquote&gt; attackspeed = data['WeaponFetchingTime'] + data['FiringTime'] &lt;/blockquote&gt; Where &lt;b&gt;WeaponFetchingTime&lt;/b&gt; is the time it takes for a weapon to begin the attack and &lt;b&gt;FiringTime&lt;/b&gt; is the time it takes to execute the attack itself. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;DoHurtAnimTime&lt;/b&gt;, pretty sure it's how long a character will be &quot;stunned&quot; by a blow. &lt;br /&gt; Attackspeed and damage is used to calculate the overall DPS a weapon can output with: &lt;blockquote&gt; data[&quot;DpsCut&quot;] = (data[&quot;CutDamageFactor&quot;] * 100.0) / attackspeed &lt;br /&gt; data[&quot;DpsPuncture&quot;] = (data[&quot;PunctureDamageFactor&quot;] * 100.0) / attackspeed &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Currently working on the new theme, takes some time as I'm switching to bootstrap and changing the full look of the site. I think that's the next thing I'm trying to finish. You can see online players and the server status on the frontpage now, just some extra useful website candy. More on the datatable keys The names in the datatable is a bit wierd and not always understandable, with time I'll make it more pretty. Right now it's just more or less a raw dump. Attackspeed of a meleeweapon in the game is calculated by: attackspeed = data['WeaponFetchingTime'] + data['FiringTime'] Where WeaponFetchingTime is the time it takes for a weapon to begin the attack and FiringTime is the time it takes to execute the attack itself. DoHurtAnimTime, pretty sure it's how long a character will be &quot;stunned&quot; by a blow. Attackspeed and damage is used to calculate the overall DPS a weapon can output with: data[&quot;DpsCut&quot;] = (data[&quot;CutDamageFactor&quot;] * 100.0) / attackspeed data[&quot;DpsPuncture&quot;] = (data[&quot;PunctureDamageFactor&quot;] * 100.0) / attackspeed</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">So many pages!</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/10/somanypages.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So many pages!"/><published>2017-02-10T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/10/somanypages</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/10/somanypages.html">&lt;p&gt; &lt;ul class=&quot;bullet&quot;&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Add analyctis&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Create a page for each item&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Worked on some different things, like setting up the analytics, I changed the datatables to single lines, Added the discord channels to the community part in the footer. &lt;br /&gt; Also now I can generate webpages from the datafiles, now I just need to place everything in appropriate places and pretty it up with some css. You can now access the item page by clicking on the weapon/armor in the datatable. &lt;a href=&quot;/cn/item/88040007/&quot;&gt;Already started to recreate the in-game card how it displays weapons.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Add analyctis Create a page for each item Worked on some different things, like setting up the analytics, I changed the datatables to single lines, Added the discord channels to the community part in the footer. Also now I can generate webpages from the datafiles, now I just need to place everything in appropriate places and pretty it up with some css. You can now access the item page by clicking on the weapon/armor in the datatable. Already started to recreate the in-game card how it displays weapons.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">tkstats.info!</title><link href="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/03/andimback.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="tkstats.info!"/><published>2017-02-03T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-03T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/03/andimback</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.tkstats.info/cn/2017/02/03/andimback.html">&lt;p&gt; Fixed a proper domain name, so welcome to tkstats.info. Seems like both a good and logical name to me.&lt;br /&gt; One step forward with this project but many left to go! I have a few things I'm thinking about to fix and add to in future. &lt;ul class=&quot;bullet&quot;&gt; &lt;li&gt;Add analyctis&lt;/li&gt; &lt;div&gt;I feel like I must add somekind of analyctis before I give the site any form of publicity.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;li&gt;About page&lt;/li&gt; &lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;li&gt;Change website theme&lt;/li&gt; &lt;div&gt;I'm currently working on a new theme using bootstrap, didn't really like the way it ended up right now.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;li&gt;Create a page for each item&lt;/li&gt; &lt;div&gt;This is a static website, so I need to either write a python script that generates all the pages or some javascript does all the work. The result should be the same but I guess it's my disk space vs page CPU load.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;li&gt;Add the forum&lt;/li&gt; &lt;div&gt;I have a been working with a disqus forum I'll integrate later when it's finished, apart from having a /forum place for &quot;general topics&quot; I'm planning that each item page that is generated should also include a comment section where you can drop a comment regarding that item.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;li&gt;Changelogs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;div&gt;I'll be saving all the patches that I datamine and make diff logs, would be nice to see what changes the weapons/armors get for each patch.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; And so on, that was a few things from off the top of my head. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;...&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- more --&gt; &lt;p&gt; Currently the data represent the values of the game patch 0.0.72, it should be fairly up-to-date by the time I'm writing this this post. Unfortunately my graphic card died recently, so a new update on the values might take a little bit longer then expected. &lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Fixed a proper domain name, so welcome to tkstats.info. Seems like both a good and logical name to me. One step forward with this project but many left to go! I have a few things I'm thinking about to fix and add to in future. Add analyctis I feel like I must add somekind of analyctis before I give the site any form of publicity. About page Change website theme I'm currently working on a new theme using bootstrap, didn't really like the way it ended up right now. Create a page for each item This is a static website, so I need to either write a python script that generates all the pages or some javascript does all the work. The result should be the same but I guess it's my disk space vs page CPU load. Add the forum I have a been working with a disqus forum I'll integrate later when it's finished, apart from having a /forum place for &quot;general topics&quot; I'm planning that each item page that is generated should also include a comment section where you can drop a comment regarding that item. Changelogs I'll be saving all the patches that I datamine and make diff logs, would be nice to see what changes the weapons/armors get for each patch. And so on, that was a few things from off the top of my head. ...</summary></entry></feed>